Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV. Film and Video Recordings, 19 Linear Feet in 17 record cartons, 2 flat boxes, and 4 oversize film cans.; 35 film reels including 20 8mm films, 1 super 8 film, 13 16mm films, and 1 35mm film.; 74 videoreels (1/2 inch); 94 videocassettes (u-matic); 7 videocassettes (betamax); 1 videocasse
  - Greatest Hits, 1991; Duration: 1:58:00 (Box 8, Vhs 267_724)
  - Greatest Hits / Duplication Tape II, November 25, 1991 (Box 16, Hi8 267_401)
  - Greatest Hits From 8mm, Undated; Duration: 01:57:00; noted as "Mono" (Box 8, Vhs 267_712)
  - Greatest Hits HiFi From 8mm, Undated; Duration: 01:57:00 (Box 8, Vhs 267_709)
  - Greatest Hits Revised, January 29, 1992 (Box 14, Hi8 267_381, Box 8, Vhs 267_733)
  - Guadalupe, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_721)
  - Hifi Master II, Including "Desperate Thought" Etc., Undated (Box 7, Vhs 267_663)
  - Heaven, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_398, Box 9, Vhs 267_692)
  - Here and There Last Take, 1976 (Box 82, Half inch video reel 267_798)
    Audio reel 267_798 was identified as moldy in October, 2021. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - HIOEOUD Work, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_556)
  - Hole, December 21, 1993 (Box 4, U-matic 267_609, Box 5, U-matic 267_623, Box 6, U-matic 267_642, Box 16, Hi8 267_391, 267_420, Box 9, Vhs 267_699, 267_704)
  - Hollywood, 1981 (Reel mss267_container6, 16mm film reels 267_011, Box 2, U-matic 267_573, 267_577, 16mm film reels 267_012)
  - Home, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Vhs 267_727)
  - Hostage, 1981 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_543)
    267_543 is a compilation tape labeled "7 California Tapes."
  - I Agree, 1990 (Box 8, Vhs 267_718)
  - I Am Talking to You: Interviews From El Paso About the World, Undated (Box 4, U-matic 267_611, Box 6, U-matic 267_640, Box 15, Hi8 267_451)
  - I Don't Know I Wanted to Go Back East But, 1980 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_551, 267_544, Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_508, Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_466, Box 82, Half inch video reel 267_468)
  - I Just Fuck Myself, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_413)
  - I Love You Amy Fisher, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_564, Box 9, Vhs 267_696, 267_692)
  - I've Got Fever, 1993 (Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
  - Ice Phantom, Undated (Box 4, U-matic 267_606, Box 9, Vhs 267_696)
  - Ice Phantom / Spectral Programs, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_424)
  - Imperilled, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_624, Box 10, Vhs 267_752)
  - Internet, May 10, 1995; Duration: Approx. 38 min (Box 7, U-matic 267_645)
  - Interruption, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_698, Box 16, Hi8 267_398)
  - Interview with Sondheim Regarding His Filmmaking, June 16, 1986; cuid34978 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_257, 267_258)
  - Into the European Mirror, 1994; Duration: 56 min (Box 8, Vhs 267_728)
  - Involuntaries, Undated; cuid39814 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_218)
  - Island, Undated (Box 2, U-matic 267_583, Box 7, Vhs 267_667, Box 16, Hi8 267_390, Box 8, Vhs 267_716, Box 10, Betamax 267_760)
  - Japan, August, 1979; Duration: Approx. 55 min (Box 2, U-matic 267_579, 267_572)
    267_579's label says, "Duplicate, without time base correction. With Alan Sondheim, Laura Hayes. Produced at Monte-Video Hartford Connecticut, John Hyjek Camera and Tech. Produced and directed by Alan Sondheim, August 1979. Screenings at Montevideo Franklin Furnace NYC Real Art Ways, Hartford." It also has an address to Sondheim's office at UCLA. 267_572's label says, "For Grant Application. This videotape is similar to my current films; the latter are masterprints only, and can only be rarely projected. Shown at: Museum of Modern Art, New York City; American Center, Paris; Kitchen, New York City. Distributed by: Art Metropole, Toronto, Canada."
  - Je Suis Sage by Kimberly Bartosik with Frederic Gafner, Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_742)
    This tape includes versions with and without subtitles. Unclear whether the subtitles are in English or in French.
  - Jennifer, February 28, 1997 (Box 16, Hi8 267_386)
  - Jennifer, Where Are You? Leslie Thornton, 1981; Duration: 10 minutes (Box 21, Vhs 267_783)
  - Jerome (Everything), Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_745)
  - Joanna Films - 1st 3 Dailywork Transfers, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_418, Box 7, Vhs 267_656)
  - Joanne, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_405)
  - Joanne - yr 300 footage, Halifax footage, Undated (Box 81, 8mm film reel 267_029, 267_030)
  - Joanne Martin / SHAVE with Ann Daly, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_438)
  - Jodee Jingles, 1993 (Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
  - Jodee Material; Vulture; Ceremony (Alice); Dragonfly; Courteway (Box 15, Hi8 267_449)
  - Jodi Drugs, Alan, Lori, Undated (Box 7, U-matic 267_650)
  - Jodie Questioning Me / Alice Questioning Me / Moving Dance in Studio w SFX / SFX w/ Police and Text / Sex Complex / Mark / Police / Sex image cycle / Alice reading, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_697)
  - Juan Davila, Undated (Box 7, Vhs 267_665)
  - "Julu Twine" by Alan Sondheim and Myk Fredman, Undated; cuid39815 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_219)
  - "Jungamer" Digital Video Series, 2004-2009; cuid39778 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_138)
  - Kabbalah, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_495)
  - Kasper Hauser in Holocaust City - Psychotic Tapes, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_400, Box 10, Betamax 267_754, Betamax 267_756)
  - Landscape, 1980 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_467, Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_549)
    267_467 is a compilation tape labeled "4 California Tapes." Its label also says, "EIAJ Black and White." 267_549 is also a compilation tape.
  - Launch, Undated (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_548)
  - Laura, 1979 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_009, Box 81, 8mm film reel 267_006)
  - Leslie Thornton - Videos and Images, 2006-2009; cuid39802 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_162)
  - "Let Me Count the Ways / Minus 10, 9, 8, 7... " - Leslie Thornton, 2004; cuid39816 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_220)
  - Lexicon, 1980-1981; cuid39771 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_477, 267_467, Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_543, 267_547, 267_550)
    267_477 is labeled as the master recording. 267_467 is a compilation tape labeled "4 California Tapes." Its label also says, "EIAJ Black and White." 267_543 is a compilation tape labeled "7 California Tapes." 267_549 and 267_550 are also compilation tapes.
  - Life (Explain), Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_390, Box 8, Vhs 267_716)
  - Life Story..., Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_440, Box 9, Vhs 267_677)
    The tape label says, "Life Story Master, AFM Sound; 1st Scene Until WD. 'Honest'; Flash 2; Then NR3 until End; (W. Jodee) + OR PCM; MOTHER, PCM NR2 6'"
  - Liquid, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_677, Box 16, Hi8 267_405)
  - Lori Tape, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_459)
  - M Wilson / Alan Sondheim, Undated; cuid30329 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_506)
  - M Wilson: Rapping Video Segment, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_506)
  - Magic in the Air - Prelinger Associates, Inc., Undated (Box 6, U-matic 267_633)
    The only label on the tape seems to be an old, recycled label and may be inaccurate.
  - Margaret, 1993; Duration: 20 minutes (Box 3, U-matic 267_589, Box 6, U-matic 267_634, 267_641, Box 16, Hi8 267_414, 267_422, Box 10, Vhs 267_750)
  - Margaret Curtis / Alan Sondheim: Four videos for preview, 1990 (Box 8, Vhs 267_719)
  - Margaret Curtis: Clear White Fruit, 1990 (Box 9, Vhs 267_688)
  - Margaret Curtis: The Girding, 1990 (Box 9, Vhs 267_688)
  - "Mars" Digital Video Series, 2004-2006; cuid39779 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_139)
  - "Massoumi" Digital Video Series, 2007-2008; cuid39780 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_140)
  - Mastering Suture - Matters Pertaining to Joan of Arc, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_597)
    Another label says, "Nikuko Make-up Raw Footage" but it is crossed out.
  - "Membrane" Digital Video Series, 2001-2002; cuid39781 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_141)
  - Memory and 1973 and Master (Box 8, Vhs 267_722)
  - Millennium, March, 2001; cuid39770 (Box 14, Minidv 267_376, 267_380, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_221)
  - Mobil #7, August 2, 1992 (Box 6, U-matic 267_635)
  - Mobil Cutting Oil #7, June 22, 1991 (Box 5, U-matic 267_615)
  - Monday Afternoon Martin, 1991 (Box 16, Hi8 267_393)
  - Mother (Pieta), 1993 (Box 9, Vhs 267_677, Box 16, Hi8 267_411, Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
  - Motherstructure, 1993 (Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
  - "Motion Sensor" Digital Video Series, 2005; cuid39782 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_142)
  - Mud, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_451, Box 6, U-matic 267_641)
  - Mullen, Undated (Box 14, Minidv 267_377)
  - Murmur, 1993; Duration: 10 min (Box 16, Hi8 267_422, Box 10, Vhs 267_750)
  - music / consciousness / gender by Benjamin Boretz, 1994-1995; Duration: 89 min (Box 9, Vhs 267_703)
    This recording contains "texts, musics, textsoundmusics, images for live speaker and prerecorded speakers, musics and images on audio and videotape." It was recorded and produced by Mary Lee Roberts, 1996.
  - Narrative Master, Undated (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_479)
  - Nature of the Universe, May 31, 1992 (Box 16, Hi8 267_387, Box 8, Vhs 267_727)
  - "Neural Architecture no.5 3.4.5," Deborah Aschheim, 2005; cuid39817 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_222)
  - News For Teaching, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_731)
  - "Night Video" Photo/Video Series, 2006-2007; cuid39783 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_143)
  - Nikuko, December 7, 1999 (Box 3, U-matic 267_598)
    The tape's label says, "Nikuko Master 12/7/99; Also Master 1, 12/6/99; The Experimental Television Center, Owego NY"
  - Notes stored with videotapes, circa 1975-2000 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - NYC FG Waterfall ACA Briarcliff Shreveport, Undated (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_024)
  - NYSCA, Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_747)
  - "Octopus" Digital Video Series, 2006; cuid39784 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_144)
  - Old Man Canadian Swim, 1991 (Box 10, Vhs 267_770, Box 9, Vhs 267_695)
  - Old Moving Car Footage, Punk Footage, Undated (Box 80, 16mm film reels 267_004, Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Old World, undated (Box 21, Vhs 267_781)
  - On the Way to the Lake, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_584, Box 7, Vhs 267_657)
  - On Your Belly, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_564, Box 9, Vhs 267_696)
  - One Day in the Life of Tryon, 1985 (Box 80, 16mm film reels 267_016)
  - Oscelloscope Films, 1970-1975 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_005)
    Original can label says "1. 2 x 3 Oscelloscope Waveform; 2. Nova Scotia Gestmal [?] Work; 3. Orseus; 4. Beth Doubled; 5. wh SEM; 6. Oscelloscope over TV, Overlaw Talking Heads; 7. Oscelloscope; 8. Chris and Don; 1972? - 1973 - 1974?"
  - Outfit, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_491, 267_497, Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_512)
  - Papago, 1977 (Box 2, U-matic 267_580)
  - Parables - ETC, 2000 (Box 14, Minidv 267_375)
  - Parables of Izanagi, 2000-2009; cuid39785 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_145)
  - Paul Stout Volume 3, 1996-2004; cuid39818 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_223)
  - Peggy and Fred in Hell (Scenes and Shots from the Series), Produced and Directed by Leslie Thornton, 1981-1991; Duration: 10 min (Box 10, Vhs 267_772, Box 8, Vhs 267_725)
  - Piece, 1991 (Box 7, Vhs 267_665, Box 9, Vhs 267_694)
  - Planet I and II, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_721)
  - Postmodern Pobre / Postmodern Sureño / Mud / Miscellaneous until end of tape, 1992-1993; Duration: 1 hour 20 min (Box 8, Vhs 267_730)
  - Postmodern Sureño, 1993; Duration: Approx. 58 min (Box 9, Vhs 267_672, 267_681, Box 7, U-matic 267_654)
    The label lists Dawnja Burris as a collaborator. Other labels on 267_672 say "Internet Video," and "Jennifer (?) Tape." 267_681's label adds, "Second Work Sample Produced During Initial Trip to El Paso/Cuidad Juarez 11/92-1/93"
  - Probe (Insertion Into An Older Tape), Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_486)
  - PTG, Undated (Box 7, Vhs 267_665, Box 9, Vhs 267_694)
  - Puppet Show, 1971 (Box 82, Half inch video reel 267_800)
  - Puppet Show / Polygons Original, October 20, 1971 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_525)
    The tape's label also says, "Aram Saroyan; 20 min; Black and White; RISD"
  - "PVDE", Undated; cuid39864 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_224)
  - Question of Little Deaths, 1991 (Box 10, Vhs 267_770, Box 15, Hi8 267_445)
  - The Raft of the Medusa: five voices on colonies, nations and histories, 1993; Duration: 1:39:00 (Box 8, Vhs 267_736)
  - Recall, Darrin Martin and Torsten Zenas Burns, 1998; Duration: 14 min (Box 8, Vhs 267_729)
    Includes contact information for Darrin Martin
  - Recent Film Transfers (Raw Materials), 1987 (Box 10, Vhs 267_763)
    This tape includes footage later used in "The Third Millennium (The Year 3000)," and footage used for Damaged Life concerts.
  - Recent Selected, July 21, 1992 (Box 10, Vhs 267_771)
  - The Reed Point Monolog - Alan Sondheim and Laura Hayes, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_492, 267_501, Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_514, 267_517, Box 6, U-matic 267_630, Box 7, U-matic 267_651)
  - Reg 8, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_737)
  - Remnants (Fold Catastrophe), 1978 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_513, 267_516, 267_524)
  - Remnants from the Beginning of the Period of Destruction by Alan Sondheim with music by A.S. and Laurie Anderson, 1977 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_476, Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_493)
  - "Ren" Digital Video Series, 2002; cuid39786 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_146)
  - Repetition, 1972 (Box 82, Half inch video reel 267_800)
  - Reverse, 1980 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_467)
    267_467 is a compilation tape labeled "4 California Tapes." The label also says, "EIAJ Black and White."
  - Reverse Wound at 000 Feet, Begin 728 to 880, Undated; cuid30333 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_537)
  - Rhythm Fest #12, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_629)
    This recording features Rhythm Fest Backstage, Girlz Nose, Lesbian Belle, and Paige.
  - Rhythm Fest - Mayday, Undated (Box 4, U-matic 267_614)
  - Ridge, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_450)
  - "Ring" Photo/Video Series, 2002; cuid39787 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_147)
  - Roam Sweet Home, a film by Ellen Spiro, 1996; Duration: 56 min (Box 10, Vhs 267_778)
  - Robin, Undated; cuid30332 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_521, 267_522)
  - Rockefeller, Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_746)
  - Rough Cut Segment, 1981 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_543)
  - "Rulers" Digital Video Series, 2006; cuid39788 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_148)
  - S.E.M. Imagery, Undated (Box 81, 8mm film reel 267_034)
  - Sample Tape, Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_779)
  - San Diego, 1981 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_543)
  - Scan, 1972 (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_498, Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_547)
    Tape 267_498's label notes that it is the original version of the recording. Tape 267_547 also includes a recording of "Wormhole Model"
  - Sequestered Geography, 1992 (Box 5, U-matic 267_627, Box 68, Folder 14)
    Includes film notes in Box 68.
  - Sexual Tape With Burglar Alarm, Undated (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_552)
  - Sexualities, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_419, Box 9, Vhs 267_686)
    According to the label of videotape 267_686, the recordings included in Sexualities emph> are "My Cunt" 1, 2, and 3, "BADBOYBADGIRL," "Milking," "Flesh and Bone," "I Want This Hole," "Body Burns," "Borders," "Arise," "Sorrow Cock," "Cunt," "Masturbate," and "Radiate."
  - She Came In and Out of Me - Film the End, 1987 (Box 80, 16mm film reels 267_018)
  - Short Road Bit, Undated (Box 81, 8mm film reel 267_036)
  - Silent Film - Neighborhood Scenes, Undated; cuid35049 (Box 25, 8mm film reel 267_054)
    Duration: 18 minutes.
  - "Ski/nn", Undated; cuid39819 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_225)
  - Skinny Was Dead, August, 1992 (Box 7, U-matic 267_652)
  - Slab, 1981 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_542, 267_543, 267_549, 267_550)
    267_542 is an empty reel - no videotape present. 267_543 is a compilation tape labeled "7 California Tapes." 267_549 and 267_550 are also compilation tapes.
  - Slate, 1980 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_467)
  - Snow / Dog / Acker Tape, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_428)
  - The Society of the Spectacle by Guy Debord (an Ediciones la Calavera Project), 1967 (Box 10, Vhs 267_764, Box 68, Folder 11)
    Includes a short note on subtitles in Box 68.
  - Some Fall Shots, Undated (Box 81, 8mm film reel 267_035)
  - Someone Dies, October 22, 1993 (Box 14, Hi8 267_383)
  - Source 1, Source 2, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_702, Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Source 3, Source 4, Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_768, Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Sorce 5, Source 6, undated (Box 21, Vhs 267_780, Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Source 9, Source 10, Undated (Box 7, Vhs 267_666, Box 68, Folder 13)
    Film notes included in Box 68.
  - Source 11, Source 12, Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_765, Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Source 13, undated (Box 21, Vhs 267_785, Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Souvenir, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_412)
  - Special Glasses, July, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_405)
    The tape's label says "1. Liquid - Unusable 7', Usable AFMvPCM NR3 7'; Clara 14' AFMvPCM NR2 Both Mastered Thru 3/4"; 3. Joanna 11' NR2 PCM, louder; Special Glasses, 23' Mixed NR 0-2."
  - Star Wars Protest (Empty Film Can), February, 1986 (Box 68)
  - Stars Come Out, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_413, Box 9, Vhs 267_698)
  - Stealing Time (Two Versions) / Collected Works / Steam, Undated (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_472)
  - Strange Space by Leslie Thornton and Ron Vawter, 1992 (Box 8, Vhs 267_732)
    A note on the cover says, "Missing head and tail credits."
  - Stub, 1981 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_543)
  - Structural Film, 1972; cuid30318 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_142)
  - "Surf" Digital Video Series, 2004; cuid39789 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_149)
  - Talking Cure, 1982 (Box 80, 16mm film reels 267_013)
  - "Tantantan", Undated; cuid39820 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_226)
  - Tasmanian Master, 1983 (Box 79, 16mm film reels 267_014)
  - Terror, December, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_420, Box 4, U-matic 267_609, Box 9, Vhs 267_704)
  - "Terror" Digital Video Series, 2001; cuid39790 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_150)
  - Testmaster, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_565)
  - These Smooth Lines Comfort Me, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_698)
  - This Is the Film in Which You Are Forgiven and This Is the Film in Which I Am Lost, 1982-1984 (Box 81, 16mm film reels 267_015)
    Original film can label says "Pia -- This is the film in which you are forgiven; This is the film in which I am lost; Silent 16-18 fps; 1982-1983; Alan Sondheim"
  - This Really Is Trying to Tell You Something, 1980 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_544)
    267_544 is a compilation tape labeled as "3 California Tapes."
  - "Tine" Photo/Video Series, 2005; cuid39792 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_152)
  - Titles ETC Master, 1997 (Box 16, Hi8 267_403)
    The tape label says "1. And Then This Happened; 2. Alan S. 1997 Thanks to ETC/FUA; 3. I Bridge My Love From Here To You Clara; 4. Yes, IX! I do love Amy Fisher, perhaps you've heard of Clare? (I40)."
  - Titling From Tape # 6, 11, 4, 9, 10, undated (Box 21, Vhs 267_786)
  - TR FAV, Undated; cuid30321 (Box 81, 8mm film reel 267_138)
  - Track, 1970-1980 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_530, Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_467, Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_550)
    267_530 is labeled as the master recording. 267_467 is a compilation tape labeled "4 California Tapes." Its label also says, "EIAJ Black and White." 267_550 is also a compilation tape.
  - Trance Films, 1991 (Box 7, Vhs 267_665, Box 10, Betamax 267_756, Box 9, Vhs 267_694)
  - Transfer Original, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_507)
  - Travel Footage - Southwest and Northeast U.S., 1975-1981 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_008)
    Despite its label, this film contains two pornographic films spliced together - not travel footage.
  - Traveller Film / Arctic Tapes, circa 1985; cuid30317 (Box 79, Super 8mm film reel 267_143)
  - Tre Interview, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_679)
  - Trials / Vincent / John / Foof / Animal / Organix, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_674)
  - Trilby by Alan Sondheim and Azure Carter, 2002 (Box 10, Vhs 267_744, Box 8, Vhs 267_711)
  - Trilby, 2002; cuid39793 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_153)
  - Tyler Stallings, 1. Inside to the Outside, 2. Hospital Thoughts, 3. Bleed, 4. Virusmachine, 5. Stale, 6. How I Colonized Myself, 1989; Duration: 1. Inside to the Outside, 4:24; 2. Hospital Thoughts, 6:49; 3. Bleed, 4:30; 4. Virusmachine, no duration notated; 5. Stale, 1:36; 6. How I Colonized Myself, 14:37. (Box 21, Vhs 267_784)
  - Untitled, 1980 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_478, 267_481, 267_483, Box 82, Half inch video reel 267_801)
    Audio reel 267_801 was identified as moldy in October, 2021. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Untitled Film with Clock, Undated (Box 81, 8mm film reel 267_141)
  - Untitled Video, 1985 (Box 80, Half inch video reel 267_031)
  - Upstairs / Tryon Tape, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_682)
  - "Vag" Digital Video Series, 2002-2006; cuid39794 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_154)
  - Vienna, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_628, Box 16, Hi8 267_415, Box 8, Vhs 267_721)
    Other labels say "Work Visuals #2" and "Mendieta Photo Stills."
  - Virgin Mary, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_413, Box 9, Vhs 267_698)
  - Vladivostok, 1977 (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_487, Box 82, Half inch video reel 267_797)
    Audio reel 267_797 was identified as moldy in October, 2021. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Vulture Until End, Undated (Box 7, Vhs 267_665)
  - Watchman Park / Frank and the Ladies / 5 Minews / Aplets Mister, Undated; Duration: Watchman Park, 09:19, Frank and the Ladies, 07:32, 5 Minews, 13:04, Aplets Mister, 25:22; a note says "Miller" (Box 8, Vhs 267_714)
  - Waveform Pulse, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_470, 267_484)
    The tape's label also says, "1. Wimhurst; 2. I Am Metaphysics; 3. Oscilloscope Voice; 4. "I Am Metaphysics"; 5. Feedback; 7; Pulse"
  - Way Out West, Undated (Box 80, 16mm film reels 267_026)
  - Wimhurst Generator Tape, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_496)
    The tape's label also says "Static Machine / Pulse Into Echo / Performance"
  - Without / Compilation Reel 3, 1972 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_538)
    The tape's label says, "1. Beth Cannon, 1972; 2. Light Mallet John Woodson 5 min, 1972; 3. John Woodson / Karin Achenbach, 1972, Information transfer; 4. Polygon 10 min, 1972; Without - 1st 6-7 minutes; Monitor image should be very dark and high contrast so that only white paint is visible - play in dark room. Fast forward to 161-839 in reverse."
  - Woman's Tape, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_500)
  - Work of Inferno [Illegible], Undated (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_023)
  - Works From Miami, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_675, Box 10, Vhs 267_749)